#云层之后#
#Unfold behind the clouds#
#彩虹之上#
#And there upon a rainbow is#
#永不完结故事的答案#
#The answer to a never-ending story#
#故事#
#Story#
普朗克常数是6.62607004
Planck's constant is 6.62607004.
你刚刚拯救了世界
You just saved the world.
我好想你 Dusty-bun
Gosh, I miss you, Dusty-bun.
我更想你 Suzie-poo
And I miss you more, Suzie-poo.
我更想你 乘以银河里所有的星星
I miss you more, multiplied by all the stars in our galaxy.
不对 我更想你...
No, I miss you...
够了
Enough.
- 操 - 走走走
- Shit! - Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
它转弯了
It's turning around.
- 什么 - 它转弯了
- What? - It's turning around!
大概被遛累了
Maybe we wore it out.
我不觉得 抓住了
I don't think so. Hold on.
所有人都出去
Hey! Everybody out.
出去
Everybody out!
准备好做个了结了吗
You ready to end this?
进去 进去
In here. In here.
好 快快快
Okay. Come on, come on, come on...
Billy
Billy.
Billy 别这样
Billy, you don't have to do this.
Billy 你叫作Billy Billy Hargrove
Billy. Your name's Billy, Billy Hargrove.
你住在樱花巷4819号 Billy 别 我是Max 我是你...
You live on 4819 Cherry Lane. Billy, please, I'm Max, I'm your...
Murray 你那边搞定了吗
Murray, you all set down there?
搞定了 这边有人来了 等你来帮忙
All set, but I've got some company which I'd love you to obliterate.
好 坚持住
Will do. Hang tight.
数到三
On three.
一...
One...
二...
Two...
发现美国人
The Americans,
他们在...
I've found them...
别害怕
Don't be afraid.
很快就结束了
It'll be over soon.
不要挣扎
Just try and stay... very still.
跟这个打吧 你个丑东西
Flay this, you ugly piece of shit!
喂 混蛋 看这边
Hey, asshole! Over here!
- 快用完了 - 我知道
- We're almost out! - I know!
Dustin 没时间了
Dustin! We're out of time!
快 快关掉
Hurry! Close it now!
关掉
Close it!
来啊
Come on!
Mike...
Mike
Mike.
Mike Mike 醒醒 听得见我说话吗
Mike. Mike. Mike, get up. Mike, can you hear me? Mike! Mike!
起来
Hey, come on.
你没事吧
You okay?
El在哪
Where's El?
- 走开 - 住手
- Leave me alone! - Stop it!
- 妈妈 - 她就是你姐姐了
- Mom! - This is your new sister.
... 至少有七英尺
... at least seven feet.
七英尺...
Seven... feet.
你和她说...
You told her...
波浪有七尺高
the wave was seven feet.
沙滩上 你跑向她
You ran to her, on the beach.
有海鸥
There were seagulls.
她戴着一顶帽子...
She wore a hat...
... 上面系着蓝色缎带
... with a blue ribbon.
穿着长裙...
A long dress...
上面有花 蓝色叶子 红色花骨朵
with a blue and red flower.
黄色凉鞋
Yell... Yellow sandals,
上面还有沙粒
covered in sand.
她很美
She was pretty.
真的很美
She was really pretty.
而你...
And you...
你很开心
you were happy.
地狱再见
I'll see you in hell!
我来
Hit me.
用完了
We're out!
操
Damn it!
不要
No!
快关掉
Close it now!
关掉
Close it!
Billy
Billy!
- El - Mike
- El. - Mike!
Billy
Billy?
Billy.
Billy Billy 起来吧 求你了
Billy, Billy, get up, please. Billy, get up, please, please.
- 抱歉 - Billy...
- I'm sorry. - Billy...
Billy Billy
Billy. Billy.
Billy 起来啊 Billy 求你了 Billy...
Billy, wake up. Billy, get up. Please, Billy...
Billy
Billy!
Billy...
很遗憾
I'm sorry.
没事的 没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
Hop
Hop.
Jim Jim呢
Jim. Where's Jim?
走 走 跟上
Let's go! Go! Come on!
你没事吧
You all right?
把手举起来
Hands up!
别开枪 美国人 我们是美国人
Don't shoot! American! We're Americans! Americans!
跟上 走
Hey, come on, let's go!
快 快
Go, go!
感谢上帝
Thank God!
三个月后
尖端时刻
欢迎来到印第安纳州 Hawkins
Welcome to Hawkins, Indiana,
一个好地方 无论是成长
a wonderful place to grow up,
养家
to raise your family,
还是遛狗 都很好
to walk your dog.
但是...
But then...
一切在独立日那天都变了
... on July Fourth, everything changed.
小镇发生一起惨剧
A terrible tragedy struck this small town.
先锋报 流言席卷小镇
Journal Tribune SCANDAL ROCKS SMALL TWON
三十人死亡
警长英勇丧身火场
市民呼唤正义
但这并不是小镇的第一起悲剧
But this was not this small town's first brush with tragedy.
离奇的死亡 政府的闪烁其辞
Mysterious deaths, government cover-ups,
古怪的化学品泄漏
a bizarre chemical leak.
这些有关联吗
Is it all linked?
是一个巨大的阴谋
All a vast conspiracy?
还是市长的不知廉耻和腐败
The fault of a disgraced, corrupt mayor?
又或是其他神秘的力量
Or is something more going on in the heartland?
小镇被诅咒了吗
Can a town itself be cursed?
是撒旦教的信徒在作怪吗
Some believe a rise in Satanism is to blame.
欲知真相如何
To find out,
请锁定今晚八点 Cutting Edge栏目
tune in tonight at 8:00 p.m. for "Horror in the Heartland"
"腹地的恐怖事件"
on Cutting Edge.
推荐人你写的你妈妈
You put your mom down as a reference?
对啊 怎么呢 她非常受人尊敬
Yeah. Why not? She's, like, super well-respected.
真是个傻子
You're such a dingus.
什么...
Wha...
说明一下 我们不是被炒鱿鱼了
Uh, just to be clear, we weren't fired, you know.
商场起火了 死了很多人
The mall burned down and, like, killed a bunch of people.
谢谢告知 刚知道
Thanks for sharing. Didn't know.
最喜欢的三部电影 开始
Three favorite movies. Go.
《公寓春光》
Uh... The Apartment,
《战国英豪》《天堂的孩子》
Hidden Fortress, Children of Paradise.
你说 开始
You, go.
- 最喜欢的电影 - 我结巴了吗
- Favorite movies? - Did I stutter?
当然有《动物屋》
Uh... Animal House, for sure.
看着我 Harrington
Eyes on me, Harrington.
好
Yeah. Uh...
《星球大战》
Star Wars.
《新希望》
A New Hope?
现在出到哪部了
A new what-now?
你说的哪部
Which Star Wars?
有泰迪熊的
The one with the teddy bears. Duh.
没有吗
No? Uh...
刚上映的那部电影 刚上映的
Oh, the one that just came out. The movie that just came out.
有DeLorean和Alex P. Keaton的
The one with the DeLorean and Alex P. Keaton,
他还想敲他妈妈
and he's trying to bang his mom.
时间...
The time...
这些就是我最喜欢的三部 非常经典
Yeah, those are my top three. Classics.
你周一来上班
You start Monday.
你就不用了
You start never.
让我们俩单独聊一分钟行吗
Will you just, um... Will you give us a minute?
为什么
Why?
Steve
Steve.
好 你要清楚 Keith
All right, you have to understand, Keith,
虽然这个傻子的品味一般
I know his taste is a bit pedestrian,
但他有其他优势
but the dingus has other qualities.
He's a douchebag of the highest order, Robin.
高中的时候他有点清高 我保证
He was a bit of a prick to us in high school, I'll grant you that,
但他还是...
but he remains...
很招人喜欢
a total chick magnet.
好吧 那跟我有关系吗
Yeah, okay, and this is relevant to me how?
Uh, Earth to Keith.
小姐姐们会来看他呀
The ladies will come in just to see him.
成群的来
They'll come in in droves.
成群啊 Keith
Droves, Keith.
我们卖了好多冰淇淋
We sold so much ice cream,
他们要从密歇根转两次船
they had to get a second shipment in from Michigan.
密歇根啊 Keith
Goddamn Michigan, Keith.
这些小姐姐
And these ladies...
身材非常好
These ladies are hot.
身材真的好
They're so very hot.
但是这么多人 小Steve一个人应付不过来
And there are too many of them for little Steve.
他需要帮助
He needs assistance.
尤其是你的帮助 Keith
He needs your assistance, Keith.
你有什么目的 你喜欢他吗
What's in it for you? You got a thing for him or something?
操 只是...
Goddammit. This is...
我们只是...
We're just, um...
朋友而已
We're just friends.
Fast Times Fast Times 听过吗
Fast Times. Fast Times. Ever heard of it?
我最喜欢的三部 Keith
Top three for me, Keith.
-
- Whoa, whoa, whoa! Slow down. - Sorry. Sorry.
- Still got it? - Yeah, yeah.